so Scrappy came out and said this go
ahead scra shout out somebody that I
dated a long time ago that bam just went
and did an interview with and didn't
even know it who Amanda seal Amanda seal
she always stand up for the women but I
wonder did she tell bam that she her her
ex-husband
for now you know why no one really knew
that conversation existed until he said
something and then somebody went to look
go ahead and and and and and look at her
try to get some rating she trying to do
it not Tasha K would never but it's the
shock Factor go ahead did you know know
that I was crap
no that moment right there you see that
face she's a
comedian she's aing comedian what a
thought cuz I didn't see funny
there